<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?>
<plan plan-format="1.0" xmlns="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
      name="Mylyn Intent">
   <release projectid="mylyn.docs.intent" version="0.8"/>
   <introduction>
     <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
     <p>
	     Mylyn Intent is an open source <b>documentation environment</b>, that allows you to <b>keep your doc
		synchronized</b> with any development artifact (Source code, Models, Dependencies...) while being
		<b>customizable</b> for your development processes (domain specific constraints, syntax or tools...).
	</p>
	</html:div>
   </introduction>
   <release_deliverables>
     <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
       <ul>
       	   <li><b>Mylyn Intent</b> : Intent generic components & authoring environment (editor, compiler, synchronizer...). Notice that it can be used in RCP mode as it is independant from core.resources</li>
           <li><b>Mylyn Intent - Workspace support</b>: Required to make Intent work on an Eclipse workspace (specific views, project wizards...)</li> 
		   <li><b>Mylyn Intent - CDO support</b>: Required to make Intent work on a CDO repository (specific views, project wizards...)</li> 
           <li><b>Mylyn Intent Connector: Java</b>: allows to directly drop java files/classes/methods inside an Intent doc an synchronize them</li>
           <li><b>Doc generators For Wikitext</b> : A set of generators for Wikitext documents (Latex, html...)</li> 
           <li><b>Doc generators For Intent document</b> : A set of generators allowing to export an Intent Project to several formats (HTML Bootstrap...)</li> 
       </ul>        
     </html:div>
   </release_deliverables>
   <release_milestones>
      <preamble>
         <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
         Mylyn Intent 0.8 is part of the Mylyn Docs 1.8, which is part of the Mylyn 3.9 release.
         Please refer to the <a href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.php?projectid=mylyn#release_milestones">Mylyn plan</a> for release milestones.   
         </html:div>
      </preamble>
      <milestone date="2013-05-22" milestone="0.8 RC1"> <html:div>Mylyn Intent 0.8 - Release candidate (API and Feature Complete)</html:div></milestone>
      <milestone date="2013-05-29" milestone="0.8 RC1"> <html:div>Mylyn Intent 0.8 - Release candidate</html:div></milestone>
      <milestone date="2013-06-05" milestone="0.8 RC1"> <html:div>Mylyn Intent 0.8 - Release candidate (API Freeze)</html:div></milestone>
      <milestone date="2013-06-12" milestone="0.8 RC1"> <html:div>Mylyn Intent 0.8 - Release candidate (Final Build)</html:div></milestone>
      <milestone date="2013-06-26" milestone="0.8 RC1"> <html:div>Mylyn Intent 0.8 - Major release</html:div></milestone>
      <postamble><html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"></html:div></postamble>
   </release_milestones>
   <target_environments>
     <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">Mylyn Docs follows the <a href="http://eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.php?projectid=mylyn#target_environments">target environment</a> guidelines of the Mylyn project.</html:div>
   <internationalization>
          <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">Mylyn Docs follows the <a href="http://eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.php?projectid=mylyn#target_environment">internationalization</a> guidelines of the Mylyn project.</html:div>
   </internationalization>
   </target_environments>
   <compatibility_with_previous_releases>
       <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">As Intent is still in incubation, there are some API changes since the 0.7 release to handle new features</html:div>
   </compatibility_with_previous_releases>
   <themes_and_priorities>
     <preamble>
         <html:div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">The main priority for Intent 0.8 is to provide the miminal set of features allowing to document
         java code, and provide a good end-user experience (completion, syntax highliting, real-time preview, exports...).
         </html:div>
     </preamble>
       <theme name="Stability & performances">
        <description> <html:div>
       Although Intent 0.8 will not be perfect in regards to those concerns, we have improved stability & performances.
        </html:div></description>
     </theme>
     <theme name="Improve end-user experience">
        <description> <html:div>
        Improve the end-user experience by:
        <ul>
        <li>Integration with EMFCompare 2 to improve sync. issues display (https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/show_bug.cgi?id=395458) </li>
        <li>Minor UI features (link with editor mechanism, improved preference page, better syntax highliting and completion...)</li>
        <li> Provide an 'Intent preview' view allowing to get real-time HTML boostrap preview of the currently opened Intent doc part</li>
        <li></li>
        </ul>
        </html:div></description>
     </theme>
     <theme name="Java bridge for Intent">
        <description> <html:div>
         We have provided a new feature allowing to directly drop java files/classes/methods inside an Intent section. You can then use ctrl+click to open a java editor on those elements, get sync. issues in real-time.
         Each reference is displayed using an Image showing the element and its javadoc (customizable).
        </html:div></description>
     </theme>
   </themes_and_priorities>
 </plan>